http://www.angelflightne.org/angel-flight-new-england/privacy.html

About UsWho We AreHistoryFast FactsAccomplishmentsBoard of DirectorsFinancialsGeneral FAQsPrivacy PolicyPhotos How to HelpOverviewDonate MoneyDonate TimeSpread the WordSponsor UsDonate NowTestimonials Patients & PassengersRequest a FlightWhere Does AFNE FlyPassenger DocumentsPatientsAngels for Armed Forces PilotsAFNE Volunteer Pilot Log-inAFNE Pilot RequirementsAFNE Pilot ApplicationFlight SafetyFuel Reimbursement ProgramFuel Rebate ProgramAFNE Pilot Go/No Go ChecklistIndividual Pilot Fund Invoice FormAFNE Pilot Fuel DonationAFNE Online Store News & EventsNewsEventsNewslettersVideosSign Up for Our Mailing List VolunteersEarth Angels / Ground CrewOther Volunteer Opportunities Contact UsAFNE Pilot Log-InAFNE Pilot Log-in AFNE Store
0
Print
Email
Privacy Policy
Angel Flight NE's (AFNE) online privacy policy governs personal information gathered on our Internet sites (www.angelflightne.org).
AFNE's Commitment to Online Security
Physical, electronic and managerial procedures have been employed to safeguard the security and integrity of personal information. AFNE encrypts billing information wherever AFNE requests it. All AFNE agents and contractors with access to personal information obtained on the AFNE web sites are also bound to adhere to this policy as part of their contract with AFNE.
Personal Information that AFNE May Collect Online
Occasionally collects personal information online, including names, postal and email addresses, phone and facsimile numbers, and billing information. AFNE does not knowingly collect or maintain any personal information from children under the age of 18. In addition, no part of our sites are designed with the purpose of attracting any person under age 18.
How AFNE Uses Personal Information Collected Online
Unless you otherwise consent, we will use your personal information only for the purpose for which it is submitted, such as to reply to your emails; handle your comments, questions, and requests for information; process applications for patients, pilots, and volunteers; and process donations. Our research may lead to the publication of aggregate demographical data but will not result in the reporting or publication of any personal information provided to us. At certain points where personal information is collected on our site, there may be a box where you may indicate you would like to be on a mailing list to receive information about other AFNE programs and services and about ways to support AFNE missions. This election box only appears in places where the department collecting personal information maintains such lists. At any time you can add or remove your name from an AFNE list by contacting us at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
.
How Your Information May Be Shared
To process a request for a free flights, AFNE's mission coordinators may send your information to an AFNE volunteer pilot who will fly the mission, and to an AFNE ground volunteer who will assist in ground transportation for the mission. By requesting a flight mission, you are allowing us to forward your information to the appropriate AFNE participants. Without submission of the requested information, the AFNE will not be able to process your request.
We never sell or rent your personal information.
AFNE may also release personal information under the following circumstances:
Where release is required by law (for example, a subpoena) or regulation or is requested by a government agency;
When a medical emergency requires it;
Where our records indicate a person may be engaged in fraudulent activity or other deceptive practices that a governmental agency should be made aware of; or
To appropriate persons, where your communication suggests possible harm to others.
Help Us Keep Your Personal Information Accurate
If your personal information changes or you would like to review the personal information we may have on file, please e-mail us with the new information or your review request at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
. Let us also know what led to your submission of personal information so we may efficiently locate your information.
Computer Tracking and Cookies
Our web sites are not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information not entered by visitors. Our site logs do generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to our sites. This information is used for internal purposes by technical support staff to provide better services to the public and may also be provided to others, but again, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information.
A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. AFNE uses non-identifying cookies to provide easier site navigation and access to password-protected areas of the web site. You can still use the AFNE sites if your browser is set to reject cookies. Our cookies do not generate personal data, do not read personal data from your machine and are never tied to anything that could be used to identify you.
Problems or Complaints with AFNE Privacy Policy
If you have a complaint about AFNE's compliance with this privacy policy, you may contact us at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
or call (978) 794-6868.
Angel Flight Northeast's Mission
To arrange free air and ground transportation so children and adults may access life-saving medical care.
Support Angel Flight NE!
